你们莉莉阿姨和马修叔叔的婚礼前几周,有些奇异的事件总会发生
In the weeks leading up to aunt Lily and Uncle Marshall's wedding, some weird stuff started happening.
我的胃怎么开始疼了?
Why does my stomach hurt?
对不起  宝贝 我早些时候吃了个冰淇淋
I'm sorry, baby. I ate a bunch of ice cream earlier today.
宝贝  你知道我们是心有灵犀的
Oh, baby, you know we're lactose-intolerant.
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
你是说你们一个人感觉到什么了
Are you suggesting that when one of you feels something,
- 另外一个也感觉得到? - 你们真是个共生体?
- the other feels it, too? - Oh, God, you guys are so codependent.
- 我们不是 - 难道不是?
- No, we're not. - Oh, really?
那天又怎么说?
What about the other day?
- 我需要些鸡蛋 - 我跟你一起去拿
- Oh, I need to get some eggs. - Oh, I'll come with you.
那是因为我们喜欢一起分享时光 不代表我们是共生体啊
Just because we like spending time together doesn't mean we're codependent.
真的吗?
Really?
那你们计划是怎么回事
Then whatever happened to your plan of spending the last two weeks
结婚两周前不是要分居?
before your wedding sleeping apart?
我们不这样是因为...
Okay, we decided not to do that because of...
指导
Logistics.
- 新婚指导 - 就是新婚指导
- Wedding logistics. - Frickin' logistics, man.
这些指导都把事情都搞乱了
They mess everything up.
你们不做是因为你们不能做到
You didn't do it because you couldn't do it.
- 我们当然可以 - 那你们咋不做啊?
- Sure we could. - Then why don't you?
你可以去我那住啊
You can stay with me.
这样会使我们的新婚夜更特别
It would make our wedding night more special.
- 好 说定了 - 好
- Okay, let's do it. - Done.
- 我去拿杯啤酒 - 我和你一起
- I'm gonna go grab a beer. - I'll come with you.
算了  我留下
No. I'll stay.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第二十集
翻译：    billyling      校对：     叶煦
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
好了  知道了  我要走了
Okay, I know. You know? I got to go.
拜
Good-bye.
我妈快把我逼...
My mom's driving me cra....
你们身上全是调料啊
God, you guys are covered in sauce.
这个呆会你们再说 我先说...
We'll get to that. Me first.
我妈因为婚礼音乐要把我逼疯了
My mom is driving me crazy about the wedding music.
她就去了牙买加一趟 突然就说
The woman takes one cruise to Jamaica, and suddenly, it's
这样的宴会不能没有爵士鼓音乐
"not a party without steel drums."
难道你们不知道别再施压
Doesn't everybody know you're not supposed to stress out
给一个就要结婚的新娘吗?!
a bride right before her wedding?!
说说调料怎么回事
Okay, sauce, go.
- 说来话长  我呆会在告诉你 - 没错儿
- Long story. I'll tell you later. - Yeah.
是个荤段子吧?
It's a dirty story, isn't it?
你们去吃饭然后 在厨房做的时候被发现了
You guys went out to dinner, did it in the kitchen and got caught.
罗宾一看就是干好事时被发现了
Scherbatsky reeks of someone who likes to get caught.
现在我有两个理由去洗干净了
Okay, now I have to wash up for two reasons.
- 你不同意 - 绝对同意
Oh, you didn't. That's right.
你真认为你能和莉莉分居两周吗?
So you and Lily really think you can spend two weeks apart?
你知道吗?巴尼
You know what, Barney?
莉莉和我没有你们说的那么夸张
Lily and I are a lot less chees than you make us out to be.
别忘了给我弄"晚安"录像带
Marshmallow, don't forget to pack my night-night tape.
晚安录像带?
Night-night tape?
你给她做了个你说的"晚安"的录像带?
Did you make a tape of you saying "night-night" to her?
- 没 - 他不是说的  是唱的
- No. - He doesn't say it. He sings it.
太温馨了
Oh, that is so sweet.
你咋不做接吻的呢? 我就喜欢看两个人欲罢不能的样子
Why don't you kiss? I love it when two chicks make out.
真该死
Damn it.
没人能在我们结婚前让我们静一静
Nobody's bought us anything cool yet off our registry.
- 都是什么啊 - 很多原因
- What's on there? - Ooh, lots of stuff.
Kitchen Aide Artisan Series牌复合橱柜
Kitchen Aide Artisan Series tilt-head stand mixer...
零售价319.99美元  还有呢?
Retail price $319.99. What else?
Dyson DC17 Animal牌吸尘器
Um, the Dyson DC17 Animal vacuum.
549.99美元  是不是有点准?
Ah, $549.99. A little greedy, don't you think?
- 你想记住我们结婚的日子啊? - 不是  我在训练
- Did you memorize our registry? - No, I'm training.
- 训练?干吗? - 正想告诉你们
- Training? For what? - I'm glad you asked.
泰德  罗宾  都过来
Ted, Robin, get in here!
你们都觉得很难和我交朋友吧? 因为我太优秀了
You guys know how it's hard to be friends with me 'cause I'm so awesome?
和你做朋友确实挺难的 继续说...
Yes, it's hard to be friends with you. Go on.
以后会越来越难的
Well, this isn't going to make it any easier.
我就要在The Price Is Right上亮相了 (猜商品价格的节目)
I am going to be on... The Price Is Right.
- 不可能! - 什么?!
- No way! - What?!
再过些天 理查・费尔兹就将叫出我的名字 (主持人的名字)
Yes, in a couple days, Rich Fields is going to call out my name,
- 我就要出场了  - 太不可思议了
- and I will come on down. - Whoa, that is so awesome.
没想到你是The Price is Right的粉丝啊
Barney, I didn't know you were such a fan of The Price is Right.
你说笑呢?
Are you kidding?
T.P.I.R.不光是个电视娱乐节目 (节目简称)
T.P.I.R. is not just an indescribably entertaining hour of television,
它也是我们整个经济制度的缩写
it's a microcosm of our entire economic system--
是资本主义的乌托邦  消费者因为他们的努力而获得奖励
a capitalist utopia, where consumers are rewarded for their persistence,
敏锐市场嗅觉 和不言放弃的精神
market acumen and intrepid spirit.
我看到了The Price Is Right的冠军
I gaze upon the glory of The Price Is Right,
我看到了美国得面貌
and I see the face of America.
它是神圣的
And it is divine.
还有帅哥坐在车里 (节目奖品是车)
Plus, you know, hot chicks on sports cars.
然后莉莉跟罗宾走了 开始了她和马修第一个晚上的分居
Then Lily headed out to Robin's for her first night away from Marshall.
我准备好了
- I'm ready! - Ta-da-da-da-da...
- 莉莉 你太美了 - 我就知道  我很漂亮
- Wow, Lily, you look so beautiful. - I know! I'm beautiful!
我是仙女般的新娘!
I'm a fairy princess!
裙子太大了
I'm too skinny for my dress!
于此同时 我正在为伴郎致词彩排
Meanwhile, I was testing out my best man toast on Marshall.
开始了
Here goes.
大家好  我是泰德・莫斯比 马修最好的朋友
Hello, everyone, I'm Ted Mosby, Marshall's best man.
- 震撼的开场白? - 相当不错
Strong opening, right? That's fantastic.
马修春季毕业后就将成为一名律师了
When Marshall graduates this spring, he'll be a lawyer.
但你们知道马修 曾经有过一次犯罪记录吗?
But did you know that Marshall has a criminal record?
对了就是开车去Cape Cod的路上
That's right, on a road trip up to Cape Cod,
马修自己开车 在路上被警察叫停下来
Marshall was pulled over for driving by himself in a car pool lane.
糟了
Oh, crap.
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
你不能在我婚礼上说这个
You cannot tell that story at my wedding.
我全家都要去
My entire family's gonna be there.
我小表弟  我妈  我祖母 我祖父  一家之长
My little cousins, my mom, my grandma, my grandpa the minister.
你祖父3年已经去世了
That grandpa died three years ago.
他最喜欢的孙子结婚
His favorite grandson is getting married, Ted.
我想他总能从阴间 抽出一天时间来参加吧
I think he can take a day off from haunting the barn to make an appearance.
Whoo!
Whoo-whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
- 选哪个 "A"还是"B" - 啥玩意?
- So which one, "A" or "B"? - What was that?
我得想好参赛出场时怎么个跑法
I have to decide how to run to contestant's row when they say,
当他们说  "巴尼  下来参赛"
"Barney Stinson, come on down!"
我没反应过来你在干吗 能再来一遍吗?
Oh, I didn't realize that's what it was. Can you do them again?
当然
Yeah, of course.
真搞笑
Hey! Very funny.
就因为这个  等我赢完所有奖项 到时候只给你们
Just for that, when I win all the prizes, the only thing you guys are getting
Rice-A-Roni和Turtle Wax (一种类似麦片的食品)和(龟牌蜡)
is Rice-A-Roni and Turtle Wax.
那300美元就这样打水漂了?
It's $300 just to take the bust in?
求你了  同情同情我吧
Oh, please, you have to have some sympathy for me.
我下周六就结婚了 我太瘦了穿不上婚纱
I'm getting married next Saturday, and I'm too skinny for my dress.
我试着增肥都不行
I lost all this weight without even trying.
还在吗?
Hello?
- 怎么了? - 她骂我"婊子"然后挂了
- What happened? - She called me a bitch and hung up.
我真不知道怎么办了 我想我必须得付300美元
Oh, I don't know what to do. I guess I'll just have to pay the $300.
就这样付300美元? 莉莉  你疯了吗?
Pay the $300? Lily, are you crazy?
这还不是问题的关键 问题在于这简直就是猛吃的许可证
This isn't a problem. It's a license to eat.
什么是你总想吃的 但是因为怕发胖不敢吃
Look, what have you always wanted to eat but didn't because it was too ridicuusly decadent?
来个法雅牌巧克力浆果酒心糖
Ooh, a Valrhona chocolate souffl? with a raspberry brandy sauce
表面还有溶香蕉和榛果
topped with caramelized bananas and hazelnut gelato.
我还有Coll Whip和半袋玉米饼 (生奶油品牌)
I have Cool Whip and half a bag of Fritos.
可以啊
Done!
希望你能满意我的新的致词
Okay, think you're gonna be happy with my new toast.
这次没有荤的了
There's nothing sexual.
这个故事是关于 你俩恋爱关系的重要时刻的
It's, uh, it's just the story of an important moment in your relationship.
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
大家好  我是泰德・莫丝比 马修最好的朋友
Hello, everyone, I'm Ted Mosby, Marshall's best man.
- 不错   很棒 - 还行吧?
- Nice. - Right? That's great.
当我们还是大一新生的时候
Back when we were all freshman
马修和莉莉刚刚进入恋爱状态
and Marshall and Lily were just a few short weeks into their relationship...
那天是凌晨4点  我说得都是实话 而且没有错过任何细节
It was 4:00 in the morning, and I'm not gonna lie, we were a wee bit wasted.
我们都饿了
We were starving.
我出去找点零食 当我回来的时候...
So I'd gone out to get us some snacks, and when I got back...
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
我知道这太快了 但我真的很高兴你这么说
I know it's soon to say it, but I'm so glad you did.
Yeah.
这就是你要当着我全家说的?
So here's what you want to talk about in front of my entire family:
喝酒  往屋里带女孩  吃垃圾食品
drinking, having a girl in my room, eating junk food.
兄弟  你都快30了 你妈听到你吃垃圾食品会不高兴吗?
Dude, you're almost 30. Your mom would be mad at you for eating junk food?
泰德  "营养学"不重要!
Yeah, Ted, 'cause nutrition's not important.
关键是  莉莉还不知道这事
Also, so Lily's never heard that story before.
当她发现我第一次 对她说我爱你的时候
How's she going to react when she finds out the first time I said "I love you" to her,
实际上是对你和Funyuns说的  她会怎样? (一种洋葱做的食品)
I was actually saying it to you and a bag of Funyuns?
那谁管啊  你确实爱她 而且你仍然爱着她啊
But who cares? You did love her. And you still do.
你确实很爱吃Funyuns而且这事不无聊 (一种洋葱做的食品)
And you're totally over Funyuns, so it's not weird.
- Hey, Lil. - Hey.
嗨?那个就行了呗?
Hey? That's it?
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
你们俩这几个晚上都是分居的
Well, you guys have been spending the last few nights apart.
我知道有的人已经 开始傻笑  哭泣  上窜下跳
I figured there'd be a lot of giggling, crying, jumping up and down,
莉莉怎么样?
and then whatever Lily would do.
直到现在我还记得 麦克莱恩酒吧的菜单
Now, one thing I remember about the bar menu at McClaren's
至少有11种油炸的开胃菜
is that there were no fewer than 11 different deep-fried appetizers.
那天晚上 莉莉阿姨都点了
That night, Aunt Lily ordered them all.
看看
Check it out.
想象一下... 想象一下 如果...
Okay, imagine... imagine, if you will,
这是The Price Is Right轮盘上 的一美元的地方
that this is the $1 space on The Price Is Right wheel.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
已经很接近了
Oh, wow, that was pretty close.
接近?
Close?
接近?!节目要求猜价准确 不是接近
Close?! It's called The Price Is Right, not The Price Is Close!
真是太槽了
Oh, man, this is bad.
如果轮盘这关过不了 我就不能进入决赛了
If I don't win the spin-off, and I can't get into the Showcase Showdown,
都白费了!全都白费了!
everything's ruined! It's all ruined!
什么白费了啊? 为什么你把这个看的这么重啊
What is ruined? Why, why is this such a big deal?
好吧  坐下吧 我给你们讲点东西就明白了
Okay, guys... sit down, I've got to tell you something.
这就是我去参加The Price Is Right的原因
The reason I'm going on The Price Is Right
因为我觉得我该去见见我生父了
is because I've decided that it's time for me to meet my real father.
- 你父亲? - 对
- Your father? - That's right.
我父亲...是鲍勃・巴克
My father... is Bob Barker.
- 你爸爸...是鲍勃・巴克? - 就是
- Your dad... is Bob Barker? - That's right.
The Price Is Right的主持人 鲍勃・巴克?
The host of The Price Is Right, Bob Barker?
就是我爸
That's Pops.
- 巴尼? - 怎么了  罗宾?
- Barney? - Yes, Robin?
在这个世界上 你怎么就会认为鲍勃・巴克是你父亲?
Why in the world do you think Bob Barker is your father?
因为我妈告诉我的 这就是为什么
Uh, because my mother told me he was, that's why.
妈  谁是我爸爸啊?
Mom, who's my dad?
学校其他孩子都知道他们爸爸是谁
All the other kids at school know who their dad is.
- 谁是我爸爸啊? - 我不知道
- Who's mine? - Oh, I don't know.
就是他
That guy.
看  爸爸  我拿到A了
Look, Dad, I got straight A's!
爸爸  猜猜我万圣节该扮谁啊?
Hey, Dad, guess who I'm going as for Halloween?
想玩棒球吗  爸爸?
Want to play some catch, Pop?
现在我要去洛杉矶 去参加这个节目
So now I'm gonna go to L.A., be on the show,
赢得最后决赛
win the Showcase Showdown,
让他为我感到骄傲 然后告诉他我的身世
make him proud of me, and then tell him who I am.
你要在国家电视台上告诉 鲍勃・巴克 你是他的儿子?
You're gonna tell Bob Barker that you're his son on national television?
你们为什么都不相信啊?
Why is this so hard for you people to believe?
放下!
Drop the popper!
莉莉必须在一周半增加5磅体重
Lily has to gain five pounds in a week and a half,
我的任务就是帮她实现这个目的
and it is my job to help her get there.
这是最好的婚礼膳食了
This is the best wedding diet ever.
- 我瘦了1磅 - 不可能啊
- I lost a pound. - That is impossible.
你已经连续3天顿顿都吃麦当劳了
You ate McDonald's every meal for three days.
我知道《超码的我》里那个家伙全吃那个
I knew that Super Size Me guy was full of it.
肯定是婚前压力的原因 我们会找到办法解决的
Well, it must be the wedding stress. We just got to up the intake.
莉莉  坐下 给我吃20粒糖
Lily Aldrin, drop and give me 20 bites of fudge!
开始?
Okay?
别细嚼慢咽  要狼吞虎咽
Don't nibble at it. Attack it!
加油  莉莉  你能吃得更多!
Come on, Lily. You can do better than that!
我不行了
I can't.
吃快点  在你体重还没达到前
Well, eat faster, before your body figures out it's full.
- 我正在吃啊 - 你要哭了啊?
I'm trying. Oh, are you gonna cry?
你要哭吗? 瘦瘦的你哭得出来吗?
You gonna cry? Skinny little baby's gonna cry?
- 吃  使劲吃 - 好吧!
- Well, eat, damn it, eat! - Okay!
我想我知道怎么做最合适的致词了
Hey, so I think I figured out how to do your toast in a completely appropriate way.
终于好了
- Finally. - Yeah.
晚上好  我是泰德・莫丝比 马修最好的朋友
Good evening. I'm Ted Mosby, Marshall's best man.
- 还是很震撼  不是吗? -恩  不错
- Still strong, right? - Great, yeah.
我非常高兴能和你们分享 去年夏天一个重要的夜晚
I'd like to share with you all a story about the momentous evening last fall
马修和莉莉一起回来
when Marshall and Lily got back together.
然后我们一直呆到晚上10点
Afterward, we stayed up till 10:00 at night,
- 一起喝巧克力牛奶 - 我滋养的太好了
- doing shots of chocolate milk. - Man, I'm well nourished right now!
钙质可以提高牙齿和骨骼的健康
Calcium promotes healthy teeth and bones.
谢谢  马修 教给我们无需酒精的乐趣
Thanks, Marshall, for teaching us you don't need alcohol to have fun.
别谢我  谢谢我父母 交给了我好的滋养方法
Oh, don't thank me. Thank my parents for teaching me good values.
我想这个部分到此为止了
Now, I wasn't supposed to hear this next part,
但是马修俯身跟莉莉窃窃私语
but Marshall leaned over to Lily and whispered.
你知道我现在想和你做什么吗?
You know what I'd like to do to you right now?
我想握着你的手
I'd like to hold your hand.
我想紧紧地握着你的手
I'd like to hold your hand so hard
让你一周都不能握手
that you're not able to shake hands for a week.
你刚才只是说想握 我的手还是真的要握我的手?
Are you just going to talk about holding my hand or are you going to hold it?
过了一会  罗宾发现他们...
Then a little later, Robin caught them...
握着对方的手
Oh, um... ...holding hands.
这真是个有趣 体现责任感的夜晚
It was a lovely and responsible night.
为马修和莉莉干杯
To Marshall and Lily.
这是我听到的最烂的致词
That's the worst toast I've ever heard, dude.
- 这简直就是无聊 - 本来就是
- It's totally boring. - Exactly.
只要你检查过的致词 就不可能有好的
It's impossible to write a good toast with you censoring me, man.
我放弃了
I give up.
我要去读跟耶稣和足迹有关的东西
I'm just going to read that thing about Jesus and the footprints.
我也放弃了 我不管穿不穿得上了
I give up, too. I don't care if my dress doesn't fit.
我实在吃不下了
I can't eat anymore.
我感觉胃都要撑破了
I-I feel like my stomach's going to explode.
我知道
I know.
莉莉和我都准备放弃了
And so, Lily and I were both about to give up,
但是如果你们能看到 莉莉穿上那婚纱确实很漂亮
but as you can all see, Lily does look beautiful in that dress,
我也在这里想大家致词
and here I am giving a toast.
这段时间我一直冥思苦想试着
You know, all this time, I'd been wracking my brain trying to
找出莉莉和马修在一起的完美时刻
pick out the perfect moment to capture Lily and Marshall as a couple.
但是我发现完美时刻不是
But then I realized the perfect moment wasn't
从他们恋爱这10年中 像大海捞针般的寻找
some needle lost in the haystack of their ten years together.
莉莉和马修完美时刻 就发生在两天前
The perfect Lily and Marshall moment happened two nights ago.
马修  干吗呢?
Marshall, what are you doing?
去浴室
Going to the bathroom.
浴室在走廊?
In the hall?
梦游
Sleepwalking?
你肯定是醒的
You're wide awake.
- 抢劫? - 兄弟
- Robbing us? - Dude.
整周他都偷偷跑到72nd的一家宾馆
Turns out, all week long he'd been sneaking out to a hotel on 72nd,
去见莉莉
to meet Lily.
- 我想你了 - 没有你我睡不着
- God, I missed you. - I can't sleep without you.
Hey, baby?
- 你能搂我一会吗? - 当然
- Would you be the big spoon for a while? - Sure, baby.
- 增重增的怎么样 - 太糟了
- How's the weight gaining going? - Ugh, terribly.
没有你我都快崩溃了
I'm too stressed out without you around.
我在这了啊
Well, I'm here now.
最终莉莉和马修 分居试验还是失败了
And so Lily and Marshall failed in their experiment with apartness,
但是他们成功让 莉莉穿上了她的婚纱
but they succeeded in getting Lily into her dress.
真的有太多太多 莉莉和马修的故事我可以讲的
You know, there really are a million things I could tell you about Lily and Marshall,
但是只有一件事你们的明白
but really, the only thing you need to know is
10年的爱情长跑
that ten years into their relationship,
他们仍然不能分开哪怕是一个晚上
they still couldn't spend a single night apart.
愿他们再也不会分开
May they never have to again.
- 为了莉莉和马修 - 为了莉莉和马修
To Lily and Marshall. To Lily and Marshall.
这个关于莉莉和马修婚礼 的故事是个不错的
Now, kids, the story of Lily and Marshall's wedding is a good one.
不管你计划的多完美...
No matter how perfectly you plan your...
等等  我再返回去
You know, wait a second, guys. I'll get to that.
首先  我要告诉你们巴尼怎么样了
First, I've got to tell you what happened with Barney.
里查  下一个参赛者的名字是什么?
Rich, what is the name of our next participant?
- 鲍勃  是巴尼! - 有请!
- Bob, it's Barney Stinson! - Come on down!
你是下一位The Price Is Right的挑战者
You're the next contestant on The Price Is Right.
天啊
Nooo. Oh, my God!
如他所愿
Working his way out.
胜利 胜利
High-five here, high-five there.
- 一个熊抱 - 天啊!
- A big old hug here. - Oh, my God!
我就知道  我很上镜
Yeah, I know, the camera loves me.
欢迎来到挑战者行列 巴尼  西服不错
Welcome to contestant's row, Barney. Nice suit.
- 谢谢  爸...鲍勃 - 这是下一个竞猜商品
- Thanks, Da... Bob. - Here is the next item up for bid!
鲍勃  时尚情侣手表 18克镀金
Bob, the stylish his-and-her watches feature an 18k gold bezel and crown
不锈钢表带
and stainless steel bands.
巴尼  你觉得价格是?
And Barney, what do you bid on that?
错
Um... Wrong.
Wrong.
错
零售价是1，349.99美元 你说了要整数 我猜1,350美元  鲍勃
Retail price is $1,349.99, so, since you round off, I'll say $1,350, Bob.
-巴尼给出的价格是1,350美元 - 真的是1,350美元吗?
- $1,350 for Barney. - So, was it $1,350?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 是它吗? - 天啊
- Was it? - Oh, my God!
新婚愉快
Happy wedding.
你仅用1秒就赢了那台摄像机
Barney, you won that camcorder in just one second!
太难忘了 我是说印象太深刻了
That is impressive. I mean impressive.
谢谢  鲍勃
Thank you, Bob.
现在你要赢得电脑的话 你将再次竞猜
Now, to win the computer, you're going to have to bid again,
我会说是你猜的价格 是高了还是低了
and again I will say higher or lower.
让观众们看看电脑的价格
And let's show the audience the price of the computer,
观众们  不要告诉我们答案
and audience, please, do not try to help us.
时间从你第一次猜价开始
And the clock will start with your first bid.
- 十亿美元 - 差远了
- $1 billion. - Lower.
我带了一些你也许感兴趣的照片
So, I brought some photos that I thought you might like to see.
- 这是我第一次过生日的照片 - 好了 巴尼
- This is me on my first birthday. - Yes, Barney.
- 这是... - 你这是干嘛?
- This is... - What are you doing?
跟我爸爸共度美好时光
Uh, spending some quality time with my dad.
非常好  但你要注意 时间在减少
That's very nice, but look, the clock is moving.
你还有16秒了  快猜价格啊
You have only about 16 seconds. Keep bidding.
- 等等  我想让你看看这张  这张照得非常好 - 继续猜价啊
- No, no, I want you to see this. This is great. - Keep bidding.
这张是我毕业的时候照的 你看我头发
This is me at my graduation. I know, the hair.
它...  不...  很好  很好
That, no, that's nice. That's nice.
你时间还有5 4 3 2 1...
You have only five, four, three, two, one...
- 999美元 - 9...
- $999. - Nine...
巴尼  你说的太准了!
Barney, you got it exactly right!
- 再次祝你们新婚快乐 - 天哪...
- Happy wedding again! - Oh, my...
说实话  鲍勃 轮盘是我唯一薄弱的项目
I have to be honest, Bob. The big wheel is the only weak part of my game.
我相信你能行  孩子
I'm sure you'll do just fine, son.
刚才你说...
Did you just...
-我准备好了  鲍勃 - 转  转  开始吧!
- I'm ready, Bob. - Do it! Do it! Here we go!
他需要转到美元区
He's looking for the dollar.
- 还在动  还在动... - 他转的劲太大了
- It's going around, and around... - Oh, no, you spun it too hard.
不是  他用力不够
No, he didn't spin it hard enough.
就要到了  巴尼
Here it comes, Barney.
转到了! 你赢了...
You got it! You won...
但是巴尼... 巴尼 你还没有过关
But Barney... Barney, you're not through.
你赢了1,000美元 已经为决赛赢得了位置
You've won $1,000. You've won a place in the showcase.
你到目前为止做的相当出色
You are doing splendidly so far.
谢谢 你... 你刚才说你为我感到骄傲?
Thank you, would you, would you say you're proud of me?
当然
Sure.
太感人的时刻了
That was kind of a weird moment.
非常好 巴尼 你已经看到第一个竞价商品了
Very well, Barney, you have seen the first showcase.
你自己想猜还是 你想把机会让给米莉?
Do you want to bid on it or do you want to pass it to Millie?
赢不了车和洗不了温泉?我让给她
Please, no car and an above-ground spa? Pass.
米莉  他把这个留给了你 你说它价格是多少?
Millie, he has passed this showcase to you. What do you bid on it?
- 17,640美元 - 17,640美元
- $17,640. - $17,640.
多了 现在我们来看看第二件竞价商品
Overbid! Now, let's see Showcase #2.
巴尼  你的竞价商品有点神秘
Barney, your showcase begins with a mystery.
我喜欢这个
Oh, I love this.
真不敢相信现在我有多激动
I can't believe how excited I am right now.
你已经看到了竞价的商品 你猜它多少钱?
Barney, you have seen your showcase. What do you bid on it?
别说 别说
Please, please.
别说
Please.
让我来
Let me.
1  8  4  2  1
1-8-4-2-1.
我非常想要这辆dune buggy! (车名)
I don't even know what we're going to do with a dune buggy, but I want it!
这件商品的实际价格是...
And the actual retail price of your showcase is...
- 14,268美元 - 14,628美元  米莉  你出局了
- $14,628. - $14,628. Millie, you are over.
太坏了
Too bad.
巴尼  你说18,421美元 是这件商品价格
Barney, you bid $18,421 on your showcase.
这件商品确切零售价是... 18,421美元  相当准确!
And the actual retail price of Barney's showcase is... $18,421 exactly right!
- 你赢得了这两件竞猜商品  巴尼 - 天啊!
- You win both showcases, Barney. - Oh, my God!
鲍勃・巴克  提醒你 注意你的宠物...
Bob Barker, reminding you, help control the pet...
在这期节目结束前 我想对你说点话
Before, before we wrap up the show, there's just something I want to say to you.
祝贺你35年来优秀的主持着 The Price Is Right
Congratulations on 35 wonderful years hosting The Price Is Right.
谢谢  巴尼
Well, thank you, Barney.
谢谢...给你们宠物做结扎吧
Thank you... Have your pets spayed or neutered.
你怎么不告诉他?
Why didn't you tell him?
只是...
Well, it's just...
如果你一辈子一直想一件事
If you lived your whole life thinking one thing,
如果一旦你发现它是假的 你会异常失落
it would be pretty devastating to find out that wasn't true.
我只是认为鲍勃 可能处理不了这个问题
I just don't think Bob could have handled it.
- 鲍勃  是的 - 也许是个好的选择
- Bob. Yeah. - Probably a good choice.
不管怎样 好消息是...
Anyway, on the bright side.
再次祝你们新婚快乐!
Happy wedding again!
这就是巴尼叔叔怎么给
And that's the story of how Uncle Barney gave
莉莉和马修婚礼时 一辆dune buggy的故事
Lily and Marshall a dune buggy for their wedding.
我想我们就要开始两周的分居了
Um, I thought since we're going to be apart for two whole weeks,
我想给你唱"晚安"歌
I would sing you your night-night song.
Night-night, Lily
It's time to go to bed, oh, my silly, little Lily Time to rest your little head
Sha-la-la-la-la
- 再来一次 泰德 - 这次不错了
- Come on, Ted. - No, it's weird.
你发誓
You promised.
Sha-la-la-la-la